Guide to the Records of the Grey Art Gallery and Study Center RG.42.5
New York University Archives
- Series V: Photographs, 1964-1984; 242848; 10 Linear Feet in 20 manuscript boxes.
  - Series I: Modern Redux, undated; 243048 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Series I: Rick Norton – Press Photos ("A Quiet Breathing"), undated; 243049 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Series I: Sheehan Window Installation, undated; 243050 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Series I: Jaar/Sheehan -– Photographs, undated; 243051 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Series I: William Brice -– Press Photos, undated; 243052 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Series I: Claudia de Monte, undated; 243053 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Series I: Simon Linke -– Paintings, undated; 243054 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Series I: Arnulf Rainer, undated; 243055 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Series I: Arnulf Rainer -– Press Photos, undated; 243056 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Series I: Ruth Abrams, undated; 243057 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Series I: Ruth Abrams, undated; 243058 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Series I: Rosalyn Drexler -– Press Photos, undated; 243059 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Series I: Abstract Appropriations, undated; 243062 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Series I: Gallatin Photographs, undated; 243063 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Series I: Viollet-Le-Duc, undated; 243082 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Series I: Black Mountain College -– Slides, undated; 243083 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Series I: Morality Tales –- NY Institute for the Humanities (Oct 16), 1985-1986; 243084 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Series I: Morality Tales, undated; 243085 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Series I: Ricardo Zulueta – Tableau Utopia, undated; 243086 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Series I: Out of Eastern Europe, undated; 243087 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Series I: Pat Keck (Small Gallery in Conj. with AVA), undated; 243088 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Series I: AVA Slides, undated; 243089 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Series I: AVA (Awards for the Visual Arts) -- Slides, undated; 243090 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Series I: Lee Gordon –- The Hooded Paintings (Small Gallery), undated; 243093 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Series I: AVA -– Press Photos, undated; 243094 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Series I: Politics and Polemics, undated; 243109 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Series I: Adolf Wolfli, undated; 243110 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Series I: Show and Tell -– Gauguin Color Trans., undated; 243111 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Series I: Show and Tell, undated; 243112 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Series I: Rosalind Solomon, undated; 243113 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Series I: Cecil Beaton, undated; 243114 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Series I: Cecil Beaton, undated; 243115 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Series I: Twelve from New York, undated; 243288 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Series I: Against Nature: Japanese Art in the 1980s, undated; 243116 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Series I: Against Nature: Japanese Art in the 1980s, undated; 243117 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Series I: Paysage Demoralize -– Press Photos and Transparencies, undated; 243118 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Series I: Gerhard Richter, undated; 243119 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Series I: Barbara Strasen, undated; 243120 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Series I: Hujar, undated; 243122 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Series I: Mark Wallinger, undated; 243123 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Series I: Xing Fe Windows, undated; 243125 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Series I: Peter Levison, undated; 243126 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Series I: Weegee, undated; 243127 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Series I: Robert Morris –- Lenders, undated; 243130 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Series I: Robert Morris, undated; 243131 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Series I: Mike Bidlo's Appropriation of Andy Warhol Bonwit Teller Window, undated; 243133 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Series I: Andy Warhol, undated; 243134 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Series I: Integrating Identity –- Black and White Photos, undated; 243136 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Series I: Integrating Identity, undated; 243137 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Series I: Interrogating Identity – Not in show, undated; 243138 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Series I: Tom Wolfe and Ken Chu (Small Gallery), undated; 243139 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Series I: Interrogating Identity –- Catalogue (Maraj Essay Draft), undated; 243140 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Series I: Mark Wallinger (Capital), undated; 243143 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Series I: Mabou Mines -– Installation, undated; 243144 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Series I: Mabou Mines, undated; 243145 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Series I: The Greens and the Sea (Small Gallery), undated; 243146 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Series I: Against Nature (Japan) – Morimura, undated; 243149 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Series I: Against Nature (Japan) – Toshiketu Endo, undated; 243151 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Series I: Against Nature (Japan) – Noburu Tsubaki, undated; 243152 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Series I: Against Nature (Japan) – Slides not in show, undated; 243153 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Series I: Interrogating Identity, undated; 243166 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Series I: Interrogating Identity -– Artists, undated; 243158 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Series I: Interrogating Identity –- Simmons/Janelle Reining Metro Pictures, undated; 243154 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Series I: Interrogating Identity –- North Carolina Museum of Art, undated; 243155 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Series I: Interrogating Identity –- Shipping, undated; 243156 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Series I: Interrogating Identity -– Works not in show and duplicates, undated; 243157 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Series I: Interrogating Identity -– English Artists (Keith Piper), undated; 243159 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Series I: Interrogating Identity –- English Artists (Roshini Kempadoo), undated; 243162 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Series I: Interrogating Identity -– English Artists, undated; 243163 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Series I: Etruscan Exhibition (1 of 2), undated; 243167 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Series I: Etruscan Exhibition (2 of 2), undated; 243168 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Series I: Hope Sandrow –- Press Photos, undated; 243170 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Series I: Luis Caballero, undated; 243171 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Series I: Interrogating Identity –- Walker Art Center Press, undated; 243173 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Series I: Elaine Reichel -– Notre Intelligence, undated; 243174 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Series I: Michael Andrews, undated; 243176 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Series I: Yasuzo Nojima, undated; 243177 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Series I: Etruscan Exhibition –- Press Photos, undated; 243178 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Series I: Etruscan Exhibition –- Research and Exhibit Materials, undated; 243179 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Series I: John Kohring (Small Gallery), undated; 243180 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Series I: Opulent Past –- Leaflet, undated; 243181 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Series I: Opulent Past, undated; 243182 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Series I: Opulent Press, undated; 243183 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Series I: Opulent Past -– Press Photos, undated; 243184 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Series I: Lily Van der Stokker (Small Gallery), undated; 243186 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Series I: Elaine Reichek -– Western Washington University, undated; 243187 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Series I: Elaine Reichek -– Schedule, undated; 243188 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Series I: Elaine Reichek -– Catalogue Photos, undated; 243189 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Series I: Elaine Reichek -– Press and Photo Material, undated; 243190 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Series I: George Platt Lynes –- Public Relations, undated; 243191 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Series I: Other Borders –- Public Relations, undated; 243192 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Series I: Other Borders –- Exhibition, undated; 243194 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Series I: Nether Art –- Hugo Kaagman, undated; 243195 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Series I: Nether Art, undated; 243197 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Series I: Jane Gifford (Small Gallery), undated; 243198 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Series I: Joshua Neustein -– The Carbon Series, undated; 243199 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Series I: Gotscho -– Press (1 of 2), undated; 243200 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Series I: Gotscho -– Press (2 of 2), undated; 243201 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Series I: Hugh Steers (Small Gallery), undated; 243202 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Series I: Jeff Gates (Windows), undated; 243203 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Series I: Camera As Weapon –- Press Points, undated; 243204 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Series I: René Santos, undated; 243205 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Series I: 1969: A Year Revisited -– Public Relations, undated; 243206 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Series I: René Santos -– Public Relations, undated; 243207 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Series I: René Santos –- Rejects, undated; 243208 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Series I: John Defazio (Small Gallery), undated; 243209 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Series I: Willie Doherty, undated; 243210 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Series I: Arne Svenson (Small Gallery), undated; 243211 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Series I: Todd Wetts, undated; 243213 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Series I: Joseph Stashkevetch (Windows), undated; 243215 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Series I: Art about AIDS -– Public Relations, undated; 243217 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Series I: Simon Patterson (Small Gallery), undated; 243219 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Series I: Anyone in New York -– Color Originals, undated; 243220 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Series I: Bill Jacobson (Small Gallery), undated; 243222 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Series I: Charles Gleyre Publicity Photos, undated; 243224 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Series I: Charles Gleyre -– Photos not in Catalogue, undated; 243228 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Series I: American Imagination and Symbolist Painting Photos, undated; 243229 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Series I: Life: The First Decade -– Publicity Photos, undated; 243230 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Series I: Artists from Japan, undated; 243231 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Series I: Traditions/Tensions -– Slides, undated; 243232 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Series I: Mark Beard (Windows), undated; 243233 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Series I: Creative Will (Multiple Sclerosis), undated; 243234 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Series I: Ann Mandelbaum, undated; 243235 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Series I: Ed McGowan (Windows), undated; 243236 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Series I: Narelle Jubelin, undated; 243241 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Series I: Tracking the Marvelous –- Publicity Photos, undated; 243243 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Series I: Tracking the Marvelous –- Photos (1 of 2), undated; 243244 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Series I: Tracking the Marvelous -– Photos (2 of 2), undated; 243245 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Series I: Walter Gay –- Publicity Photos, undated; 243249 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Series I: Walter Gay -– Photographs and Negatives, undated; 243251 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Series I: Sheldon Levinson, undated; 243252 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Series I: Sheldon Levinson –- Press, undated; 243254 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Series I: The Photography of Space, undated; 243255 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Series I: Perceiving Modern Sculpture -– Sources of Information (1 of 2), undated; 243256 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Series I: Perceiving Modern Sculpture –- Sources of Information (2 of 2), undated; 243259 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Series I: Perceiving Modern Sculpture: Selections for the Sighted and Non-Sighted -– Publicity (1 of 2), undated; 243260 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Series I: Perceiving Modern Sculpture: Selections for the Sighted and Non-Sighted -– Publicity (2 of 2), undated; 243261 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Series I: Krasner and Pollock (1 of 4), undated; 243262 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Series I: Krasner and Pollock (2 of 4), undated; 243263 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Series I: Krasner and Pollock (3 of 4), undated; 243264 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Series I: Krasner and Pollock (4 of 4), undated; 243265 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Series I: Burra/Nash Color, undated; 243266 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Series I: Burra/Nash Photos, undated; 243267 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Series I: Burra and Nash –- Burra Lounge, undated; 243268 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Series I: Krasner and Pollock -– Catalogue, undated; 243269 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Series I: Tanya Grosman (Small Gallery), undated; 243270 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Series I: Sesquicentennial Exhibition -– Brandemus Collection, undated; 243277 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Series I: Sesquicentennial Celebration -– Ralph Fasunella, undated; 243278 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Series I: Space Photography -– Richard Manner Auxiliary Loans, undated; 243279 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Series I: Space Photography, undated; 243280 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Series I: Court of Benin -– Press/Literature, undated; 243281 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Series I: David Hockney –- Billboard, undated; 243282 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Series I: Charles Gleyre, undated; 243283 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Series I: American Painting –- Artist File, undated; 243284 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Series I: Charles Gleyre –- Licht Collection Loan, undated; 243285 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Series I: American Symbolist, undated; 243286 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Series I: Walter Gay -– Catalogue, undated; 243287 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Grey Art Gallery photograph from Triangle Fire commemoration, 2011 (Box 47)